wonderglee.com 2014-06-12

# Iminent -Free download: Smileys, Emoticons & Games for Facebook, Messengers & Emails!

Last Updated Date: 04-29-2014

IMINENT provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of search.iminent.com or start.iminent.com (the **Site** ) and IMINENT products Iminent, SearchTheWeb (or StartWeb) and the IMINENT TOOLBAR (collectively the **Application** ).

Iminent Minibar is IMINENT proprietary software that facilitates creation and usage of content such as emoticons, winks and fire nudges that can be used in online communications through services including but not limited to AOL Instant Messenger, Yahoo! Messenger, Google Talk, AOL Mail, Gmail and Yahoo! Mail. The Iminent Minibar also includes search feature that allows users to search the internet through IMINENT’s search properties. The IMINENT TOOLBAR is IMINENT proprietary software that provides an internet browser toolbar that allows users to access features including but not limited to games, winks, emoticons, mood avatars, favorite websites, popup blockers and email notifications.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site and from your use of the Application. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible at <http://www.iminent.com/support/eula/>. 

As used in this policy, the terms using and processing information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, the Application and features and content relating thereto (together, the **Service** ) and to enable users to enjoy the Service.

•In order to access certain features of the Service, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you ( **Personal Information** ). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your username and email address. Your username does not have to be your real name, it will be whatever name you choose as your username, however it will be deemed Personal Information if it is your real name. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service to you and administer your inquiries.

•We collect other information when you visit the Site and/or install one or more of the Application components, including your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type or version, operating system type or version or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site and by using the Application, access times and dates, usage statistics for your use of the Application and other statistics ( **Non-Identifying Information** ). We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Application and for the Site's technical administration, to increase our Site and Application's functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Site and Application to our visitors' needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site or use the Application, it will recognize you and serve accurate search results, advertisements and other information to you appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to localize your usage of the Services and make appropriate adaptations on country by country basis. We do not treat Non-Identifying Information as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

•The Iminent application search feature, in the course of processing a given search query, sends a request to our servers. This request includes the keyword query, time of day, browser type, default language setting, and IP address, an anonymous unique ID. We use this information to properly process your search request. For example, this data provides us with information on which language you prefer to use and your geographical location. Such information is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis, is kept strictly anonymous and is Non-Identifying Information. In addition, all information about search activity is evaluated only on an aggregated basis (except in response to a customer service inquiry or legal process).

•Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers in a way that enables you to be identified (for example, combining your browser type with your email address). But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other IMINENT users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

•Iminent Minibar leaves some log files in the temporary folder %temp%\Iminent\Log named IMBooster.msi.log and IMinentToolbar.msi.log after uninstall. The files are created during the installation of our application to log potential errors that could occur during the installation procedure. The files are not necessary to use Iminent Minibar's application and services and you can delete them whenever you want. Some files and registry settings will remain on the User's computer after the software is uninstalled to enable us to assist you in case of problems, and to detect if a toolbar is installed more than once.Multiple install information is required so that we can more accurately report install statistics to our affiliates.

## Cookies

Like many websites and services, we use cookies to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your username and password for future logins to the Site or Application, if applicable, and to store your user preferences. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site and Application, to better understand how you interact with the Site and Application and to monitor aggregate usage by IMINENT users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Application and then close your browser. A cookie does not allow us to obtain any personally identifiable information (such as your real name or address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using the Site or the Application. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Application.

## Email

IMINENT SA will offer to send an email about Iminent to your friends via our Invite Your Friends feature. When you invite your friends they will only receive one invitation email from you. You and your friends will not receive any additional emails from IMINENT or any other third party.  
Your email address and you friends email addresses, when we have them stored in our database, are protected by IMinent by restricting access to the database.   
If you wish to remove your email address from our database you can do it by clicking the link at the end of the email you received or by writing to [support@iminent.com](mailto:support@iminent.com).

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as phishing are of great concern to IMINENT. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your username, password or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the US Federal Trade Commission's website.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information_. We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

_Service Providers_. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related actions (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site or Application's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Application are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_. IMINENT cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of IMINENT or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

_Business Transfers_. IMINENT may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All users who provide Personal Information to IMINENT may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided to us by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us at [support@iminent.com](mailto:support@iminent.com) with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. You may also uninstall the Application at any time. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

## Security

IMINENT is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United Kingdom and choose to provide information to us, IMINENT transfers Personal Information to the United Kingdom and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

You will be presented with and have access to links to other websites through your use of our Site and the Application. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## Our Policy Toward Children

This Site, Application and Service are not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [contact@iminent.com](mailto:contact@iminent.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

## Contacting Us

IMINENT  
Attention: Privacy Issues  
20, Rue Bouvier, 75011 Paris, France  
Address: [support@iminent.com](mailto:support@iminent.com).

Iminent is compatible with : Windows Xp, Vista, 7, 8 & Internet Explorer 9.0 or higher, Mozilla Firefox 27 or higher and Chrome 32 or higher.  Learn more

Microsoft, Twitter, Yahoo and other properties whose names may appear on our site or within Iminent or Imbooster and its associated elements are trademarks of their respective owners. The use of these tradenames is purely informative and exemplary – it does not connote sponsorship, authorization, or endorsement of Sien SA.
